<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>HungryGreenHippo</title>
 <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com"/>
 <updated>2017-02-08T04:06:32+00:00</updated>
 <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/atom.xml</id>
 <author>
   <name>Will Koehler</name>
   <uri>http://hungrygreenhippo.com</uri>
 </author>
 
 
 <entry>
   <title>Roll-out | Vegan Cinnamon Rolls</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/Roll-out-vegan-cinnamon-rolls/"/>
   <published>2015-06-28T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/Roll-out-vegan-cinnamon-rolls</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Enjoy the smell of Cinnabon without the unhealthy cholesterol ! Here is a great recipe for VEGAN cinnamon rolls.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Dough- 1 Cup white all-purpose flour, ¼ tsp salt ,2 tbsp. white sugar, 1 packet of dry yeast, 1 tsp. Coconut oil, ¼ cup water&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cinnamon Spread- 2 table spoons of coconut oil, half a cup of cinnamon, 1/4 a cup of brown sugar, a pinch of salt&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Procedure:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once dough mixture is complete, you have to let it rise for 4 hours. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Roll the dough out&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Spread the Cinnamon Spread all over the dough like you’re painting a wall&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After, roll it &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Once rolled, cut into sections&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Put these sections which now are your&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt;cinnamon rolls, onto a wax sheet in a pan&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Put the pan and bake it in the oven&lt;/strong&gt;
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Oven should be 375 degrees&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You should bake these cinnamon rolls until they’re golden brown (at least 45 minutes)    &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Raw’esome Spinach Marinara Recipe (oil-free)</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/rawesome-spinach-marinara-recipe-oil-free/"/>
   <published>2015-06-23T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/rawesome-spinach-marinara-recipe-oil-free</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;If you’re keeping it cool for the summer, this is recipe is for you. This recipe is RAW, GLUTEN FREE, OIL FREE, and VEGAN. It’s simple to make (really simple, it only took 2 mins tops)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients&lt;/strong&gt;for marinara :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/8 of onion&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;handful of spinach&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1/2 glass of water&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;couple of basil leaves&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;one spoonful of oregano&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;CREATE:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Put all the ingredients into a VitaMix&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Blend for 25 seconds, varying intensities&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Cool if you want it to be thicker&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>No-Oil Tofu ‘Fry’ Video Tutorial</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/no-oil-tofu-fry-video-tutorial/"/>
   <published>2015-06-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/no-oil-tofu-fry-video-tutorial</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Here’s a simple and quick video for those of you are HCLF (high-carb low fat) and do not want to use oil unnecessarily (save that money $$$). All you’ll need is water &amp;amp; tofu!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>A Sweet (Potato+ Black Bean) Burger Recipe</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/a-sweet-potato-black-bean-burger-recipe/"/>
   <published>2015-06-14T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/a-sweet-potato-black-bean-burger-recipe</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I used to pay $12 for a vegan burger when I went out. Now, I can make it at home for a much cheaper price. Eating healthy and affordable :) — just what my college self loves(needs!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Ingredients :&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;-2 tsp of salt
-1 tbsp of dry garlic powder
-1 tsp of dry parsley
-1 tsp of black pepper
-1/4 tsp of cayenne pepper
-1/4 tsp of dry ginger
-1/4 tsp of dry cumin powder
-1 tsp of dry coriander powder
-16 oz of dry black beans
-1 small onion
-1 small red pepper
-Sweet potatoes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Directions:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Soak the dry black beans in water overnight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;em&gt;Turn on the stove &lt;/em&gt;+ Put the beans in a pot with 3 cups of water for an hour until it’s cooked&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Drain excess water out&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take the beans and add the ingredients listed in green &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Chop the onion + red pepper into little pieces&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sauté the onion and pepper into a pan for 5 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;SWEET POTATO TIME: Take how many sweet potatoes you want(I chose 2)
    &lt;ol&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Boil sweet potatoes in water for 15 minutes&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Peel skin&lt;/li&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cut into tiny pieces&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ol&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take the black beans and add the sautéd mixture and the sweet potatoes&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mash the newly created mixture&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Make burger patties + cook on a pan&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Split Pea Soup</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/split-pea-soup/"/>
   <published>2015-01-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/split-pea-soup</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;It’s been so cold outside lately! Whenever I walk outside, my whole body turns into an icicle. I am totally a spring/summer kind of person, and I am proud of myself for even attempting to step outside into the cold.I made this soup because I needed to warm up my insides. Here is how you make it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 cloves of garlic&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 celery stalk&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;2 carrots&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A bag of split peas&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Black pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preparing the water: 
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Boil split peas in water with a teaspoon of sea salt.&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Preparing the veggies:
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Cut two carrots&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chop One celery stalk&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mince two cloves of garlic&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Adding all the ingredients into a pot
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;In a  separate pot, put 1 tablespoon of olive oil on medium heat. Then Add celery and carrots which you then will  sauté for 5 minutes. Then add garlic and half teaspoon red chili powder and 2 teaspoons of sea salt saute for 1 minute.Add cooked split pea mix and cook for 5 minutes. Lastly, add 1/4 teaspoon black pepper&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Say “Fheese!” (Fake ‘Ricotta Cheese’ Filling)</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/say-fheese-fake-ricotta-cheese-filling/"/>
   <published>2015-01-21T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/say-fheese-fake-ricotta-cheese-filling</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My childhood was covered in cheese. I remember growing up, and making quick meals by taking vegetables, and melt cheese on top of it ( I thought I was being healthy!). Also, frozen pizzas were a must, and always stocked in my fridge. Growing up, cheese was my best friend. When transitioning into becoming a vegan, giving up cheese was the hardest part. But, then, because of my genius mother, I didn’t have to! This filling recipe which my mother crafted HAS to be shared. It tastes identical to that of ricotta cheese a person uses in ravioli, manicotti, etc. Even when my cousins come over to eat, and we make this recipe, they do not know (and they still don’t unitl now) that it isn’t real cheese! This past week, I used it to fill Manicotti.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here is what you will need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Organic Extra Firm Tofu &lt;strong&gt;15 ounces&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A bag of ‘Mozerella’ Daiya Cheese  (Can be bought at Stop n Shop &lt;strong&gt;but &lt;/strong&gt;if you are cooking for a large group or party, I would buy in bulk. Here is where you can get a bulk of Daiya Cheese:&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00CHUGJA6/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00CHUGJA6&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=hungrygreenhi-20&amp;amp;linkId=547N5DYBO26WW6I7&quot;&gt;Daiya Mozzarella Style Shreds, 8 Ounce — 12 per case.&lt;/a&gt;Most of the times when I go to the grocery store, almost all the Daiya is gone, so Amazon is a safe bet!&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Organic Baby Spinach &lt;strong&gt;20 leaves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Olive Oil &lt;strong&gt;1/4 tsp &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dry oregano &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sea Salt &lt;strong&gt;1 tsp&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Basil &lt;strong&gt;2 leaves&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Black Pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this recipe, an essential tool to have is a food processor–I used a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00KM03KKA/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00KM03KKA&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=hungrygreenhi-20&amp;amp;linkId=GU72DWEFKDTUITCA&quot;&gt;Vitamix&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Prepare the Tofu:Drain the water out of the tofu,  and place the tofu into your food processor. (The tofu is going to act as the ‘cheese’ in the way that it will offer the same kind of consistency or feeling when you eat it. ) Do &lt;strong&gt;not&lt;/strong&gt; turn on the food processor yet.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Add Taste to Tofu: The taste of the tofu comes after the other ingredients are added to the food processor. Add 20 leaves of baby spinach, 2 leaves of basil, a quarter of a tsp of olive oil, a tsp of sea salt, and a pinch of both black pepper and dry oregano.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Mix! : When you are done adding all the ingredients into your food processor. Pulse _(turn the food processor off and on in cycles) _your mixture for a few minutes. Stop when the consistency you desire is achieved!&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>FYI: Skin Health Benefits from Spices</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/fyi-spices-that-benefit-skin/"/>
   <published>2015-01-05T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/fyi-spices-that-benefit-skin</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;On my instagram, @hungrygreenhippo, I introduced a tea that I make daily. It is simply hot water with 3 spices added to it. These spices are: turmeric, coriander, and cumin!This tea is a lifesaver. It has kept my acne down, and for that, I am thankful. I literally do not have to wear cover-up anymore or try to hide my red acne spots with hair. These three spices are highly beneficial, and here is why&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ol&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Turmeric:&lt;/strong&gt; Turmeric helps fight acne because of its antiseptic and antibacterial properties. It is common in the Indian culture to rub turmeric paste on one’s skin to get rid of discoloration, acne, and to make one’s overall complexion glow. Turmeric is also helpful in the reduction of wrinkles and dark circles! &lt;em&gt;Also, from personal experience, turmeric mixed with lemon makes a GREAT exfoliator. If you want to know more about this mask, please comment, and I can make a tutorial! :)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Coriander:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;strong&gt; &lt;/strong&gt;Coriander is known to help fight problems such as eczema, rashes, and inflammation.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cumin: &lt;/strong&gt; Cumin helps fight aging because it contains high amounts of Vitamin E. If you suffer from itchy, burning skin then a glass of water with cumin mixed in it helps reduce this burning and itching sensation. &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Who needs expensive skin care treatments?&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Winter Veggetti</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/winter-veggetti/"/>
   <published>2015-01-04T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/winter-veggetti</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;Ever since my family got a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B00IIVRB3W/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B00IIVRB3W&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=hungrygreenhi-20&amp;amp;linkId=LRFFVUGA4FEW5OMP&quot;&gt;Veggetti Spiral Vegetable Maker&lt;/a&gt;, we have been using it nonstop. It is a great investment because not only does it give you nicely cut pieces of whatever vegetable you choose to use, but it is SO much fun to use! If you’re in college, or have children, this tool is so handy and portable, and can be used to make fresh veggetti where ever you are.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Veggetti, for those of you who do not know, is a type of raw pasta usually made from zucchini. No cooking is needed to make this type of ‘pasta’. The way the zucchini comes out of the Veggetti maker looks like spaghetti hence the combination of the words veggie and spaghetti to make the word, “veggetti”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;This recipe calls for 1 zucchini in order to make 2 bowls of Winter Veggetti; the recipe is called Winter Veggetti because since it is so cold out, raw food is harder to eat, so I added some warm marinara sauce on top. &lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 zucchini&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A jar of your favorite pasta sauce&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Coconut oil (or any oil of your choosing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Making the veggetti :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take your &lt;strong&gt;Veggetti Spiral Vegetable Cutter &lt;/strong&gt;(this can be found at Kohls, Target, &amp;amp; Bed Bath &amp;amp; Beyond) and place your zucchini in the cutting side. Twists your wrists, and keep moving them in a spiral motion until there is no zucchini left.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Making the sauce:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This part is fairly simple. Take a pot, add a spoonful of coconut oil, and then add your sauce. Then let it sit for 5 minutes. Turn the fire off.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pour this sauce on your veggetti, and ta-da, you are done!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Berry Big Sweet Tooth Smoothie</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/berry-big-sweet-tooth-2/"/>
   <published>2015-01-02T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/berry-big-sweet-tooth-2</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;I hope everyone had a healthy and happy new year! I cannot wait to make the best out of 2015. This recipe is for those who have a sweet tooth, but want to stay away from refined sugars. For me, I went through a period where I was feeling defeated by the vegan options I was presented, and I would find the loopholes in being vegan. PETA had a list of junk food that was also vegan, it was called,”Accidentally Vegan Food List”, and it included Hershey’s Chocolate Syrup, Cinnamon Poptarts, English Muffins, etc. (YUCK).I realized that this was not the way I wanted to go about living a vegan lifestyle; I think I was eating worse than before!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe has no refined sugars, and can be made in literally &lt;strong&gt;2 minutes&lt;/strong&gt;. (And it tastes really, really good!)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 whole banana&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Frozen berry mix&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Orange juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1.Prepare the ingredients for mixture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Peel 1 banana and place into a VitaMix (any blender is fine, but I prefer this one)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Take 3 handfuls of frozen berries and place into Vitamix&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Pour half a glass of orange juice into Vitamix&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2. Mix! :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I put my Vitamix on 6, and I started to blend. Blend it 30 seconds, or whenever you find the consistency that you desire.&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>Tamari Tofu Delight</title>
   <link href="http://hungrygreenhippo.com/tamari-tofu-delight/"/>
   <published>2014-12-29T00:00:00+00:00</published>
   <updated>2014-10-17T12:00:00-04:00</updated>
   <id>http://hungrygreenhippo.com/tamari-tofu-delight</id>
   <content type="html">&lt;p&gt;My friends always tell me that they would be vegan, but ‘it is too hard’. Becoming vegan, or maintaining a vegan lifestyle shouldn’t be seen as difficult, or time consuming.  I always strive for efficiency when I am cooking, and honestly finding out how to cook meals quick and easy is invigorating!&lt;strong&gt; This meal only took 15 minutes to make! :) &lt;/strong&gt;It’s perfect for those who like Asian cuisine, and need a quick, healthy fix. Here is what you will need:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sprouted Tofu( I got mine from Trader Joe’s aka my go to store)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Broccoli&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.amazon.com/gp/product/B0004LZJ9C/ref=as_li_tl?ie=UTF8&amp;amp;camp=1789&amp;amp;creative=390957&amp;amp;creativeASIN=B0004LZJ9C&amp;amp;linkCode=as2&amp;amp;tag=hungrygreenhi-20&amp;amp;linkId=IU6BKLGN4P65BB6X&quot;&gt;Gluten Free Tamari Sauce &lt;/a&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://ir-na.amazon-adsystem.com/e/ir?t=hungrygreenhi-20&amp;amp;l=as2&amp;amp;o=1&amp;amp;a=B0004LZJ9C&quot; alt=&quot;Image&quot; /&gt; (Most Tamari sauces have no wheat, so if you are _gluten free _check out this sauce)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Baby Bella Mushrooms&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sesame Oil&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Sea Salt&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Red Chili Paste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Directions:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;1. Pan sear the tofu:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the cut tofu squares and pan sear them in sesame oil until each side is golden brown. Put these tofu squares aside on a plate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Pan sear= Pan-searing uses high heat to seal in juices by forming a delicious crust. The key to pan-searing is making sure the pan is hot enough. To test a pan for readiness, sprinkle a drop of water onto the pan; the water should sizzle or jump around. (Cooking School: How to Pan Sear, Martha Stewart)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;2.Cook the vegetables: &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take a pan, place it on the stove, and add red chili paste &amp;amp; sesame oil. Then let that cook until the chili paste starts to bubble. Then take cut vegetables (mushrooms and broccoli) and throw it in the pan.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;~5 minutes later~&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;3.Add tofu to vegetable mixture:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Take the tofu that was just cooked, and add it to the vegetable mixture which is still cooking. Mix the mixture together. Then add 4 tablespoonfuls of Tamari sauce. &lt;em&gt;_The reason why you add the Tamari sauce last is because you want to retain flavor, and not have evaporate because of the high heat&lt;/em&gt;. _Finish it off with sea salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code class=&quot;language-html&quot; data-lang=&quot;html&quot;&gt;`/srv/www/your_app_name/shared/log/production.log`&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then you are done! :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Enjoy!&lt;/strong&gt; Let me know if you tried it!&lt;/p&gt;
</content>
 </entry>
 
 
</feed>